♪The stars remember♪
♪النجوم تتذكر♪
♪The promise we made to each other♪
♪الوعد الذي قطعناه لبعضنا البعض♪
♪Every breeze carries your touch♪
♪كل نسيم يحمل لمستك♪
♪Kissing the warmth of my hand♪
♪تقبيل دفء يدي♪
♪So no matter how far it may be, don't hesitate♪
♪لذا مهما كان الأمر بعيدًا، فلا تتردد♪
♪Love will guide us through♪
♪الحب سوف يرشدنا خلال♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would I have met you a little sooner?♪
♪هل كنت سألتقي بك في وقت أقرب؟♪
♪Like night embracing the fireworks' glow♪
♪مثل الليل يحتضن توهج الألعاب النارية♪
♪You and I were meant to hold hands♪
♪لقد كان من المفترض أن نمسك أيدي بعضنا البعض♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would destiny have brought us together?♪
♪هل كان القدر سيجمعنا معًا؟♪
♪Turning thorns into silver threads on a crown♪
♪تحويل الأشواك إلى خيوط فضية على التاج♪
♪I'll weave them for you, forever around♪
♪سأنسجها لك، إلى الأبد حولك♪
=Long Planned Love=
=الحب المخطط له منذ فترة طويلة=
=Episode 9=
=الحلقة 9=
Qin Zhuo,
تشين تشو,
your apology to me doesn't really help.
اعتذارك لي لا يساعدني حقًا.
After all, this injury of mine
بعد كل هذا، هذه الإصابة التي أصابتني
wasn't caused by you.
لم يكن بسببك.
Mrs. Zhou,
السيدة تشو،
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Ms. Mi,
السيدة مي،
don't feel too wronged.
لا تشعر بالظلم كثيرا.
If you hadn't shown me those photos,
لو لم تظهر لي تلك الصور،
I wouldn't have acted.
لن اتصرف .
We wouldn't be in this mess.
لن نكون في هذه الفوضى.
When did I ever show you photos?
متى عرضت لك الصور؟
You...
أنت...
That's suspicious.
هذا مشبوه.
She really did show me.
لقد أظهرت لي ذلك حقا.
The place you hit me has cameras.
المكان الذي ضربتني فيه كاميرات.
I saw it.
لقد رأيته.
I know I've got nothing to hide.
أعلم أنني لا أخفي شيئًا.
If you've got nothing to hide,
إذا لم يكن لديك ما تخفيه،
show me the footage.
أرني اللقطات.
Qin Zhuo.
تشين تشو.
Mm.
مم.
Tang said
قال تانغ
she trusts you completely.
إنها تثق بك تمامًا.
She said
قالت
you'd never cheat while engaged.
لن تغش أبدًا أثناء خطوبتك.
You don't seem like
لا يبدو أنك
a playboy.
رجل زير نساء.
So,
لذا،
did you actually kiss Mi Shan?
هل قمت بتقبيل مي شان فعليا؟
No, I didn't.
لا، لم أفعل.
No kiss at all.
لا قبلة على الإطلاق.
So,
لذا،
that photo was edited then?
هل تم تعديل تلك الصورة إذن؟
I thought it looked fake.
اعتقدت أنه يبدو مزيفًا.
Ms. Mi.
السيدة مي
You and I
أنت وأنا
kind of met through a clash.
نوع من التقيا من خلال صدام.
I'm actually a photographer.
أنا في الواقع مصور.
If you need photo edits again,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى تحرير الصور مرة أخرى،
just call me.
فقط اتصل بي.
I'll give you a 0.01% discount.
سأعطيك خصمًا قدره 0.01٪.
Mr. Zhou, Cheng's wound must stay dry.
السيد تشو، يجب أن يبقى جرح تشنغ جافًا.
Take good care of her.
اعتني بها جيدا.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
I'm fine, don't worry.
أنا بخير، لا تقلق.
Leaving with her or with me?
الرحيل معها أم معي؟
I've still got something to do.
لا زال لدي شيء لأفعله.
- I'll talk to her... - Whatever.
- سأتحدث معها... - لا يهم.
You go...
اذهب أنت...
Qin Zhuo.
تشين تشو.
I'll deal with you.
سأتعامل معك.
Qin Zhuo, Qin Zhuo.
تشين تشو، تشين تشو.
It's too late today.
لقد فات الأوان اليوم.
Go to bed first.
اذهب إلى السرير أولاً.
We'll pack up tomorrow.
سنقوم بحزم أمتعتنا غدا.
Alright?
على ما يرام؟
Zhou Tingyan, promise me this now.
تشو تينغيان، وعدني بهذا الآن.
And you can do anything
ويمكنك فعل أي شيء
when we're back home.
عندما نعود إلى المنزل.
Sir.
سيد.
Get the toiletries ready for her.
جهزي أدوات النظافة الشخصية لها.
Prepare her bath.
جهزي حمامها.
(So he really does want to...)
(لذا فهو يريد ذلك حقًا...)
Alright.
على ما يرام.
We're home.
نحن في المنزل.
Time to open your eyes.
حان الوقت لفتح عينيك.
You knew I was awake all along.
لقد عرفت أنني كنت مستيقظا طوال الوقت.
♪Late at night, I count the fleeting seconds♪
♪في وقت متأخر من الليل، أحسب الثواني العابرة♪
♪Among the crowd, I search for your gaze♪
♪بين الحشد، أبحث عن نظراتك♪
I never proposed to you
لم أتقدم لك بطلب الزواج مطلقا
and I didn't give you a wedding either.
ولم أقم لك حفل زفاف أيضًا.
Not a single ritual we should have had.
لم يكن ينبغي لنا أن نمارس أي طقوس.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
♪So I protect, never daring to ask for more♪
♪لذا فأنا أحمي، ولا أجرؤ أبدًا على طلب المزيد♪
♪My eyes follow with a devotion♪
♪عيناي تتبع ذلك بإخلاص♪
I don't know what style you'd like.
لا أعرف ما هو الأسلوب الذي تريده.
So I picked this pair on my own.
لذلك اخترت هذا الزوج بنفسي.
The saleswoman said
قالت البائعة
this ring symbolizes purity and uniqueness.
يرمز هذا الخاتم إلى النقاء والتفرد.
Only pure love can truly last.
الحب النقي فقط هو الذي يمكن أن يدوم حقا.
Maybe our marriage isn't that pure.
ربما زواجنا ليس نقيا إلى هذه الدرجة.
But I want it to last forever.
ولكنني أريده أن يدوم إلى الأبد.
♪The heart is as fragile as glass♪
♪القلب هش كالزجاج♪
♪Longing always comes during the night♪
♪الشوق يأتي دائمًا أثناء الليل♪
Zhou Tingyan,
تشو تينغيان,
I was the one
انا كنت الشخص
who forced you into marrying me.
من أجبرك على الزواج مني؟
You don't need to keep feeling guilty.
لا داعي لأن تشعر بالذنب باستمرار.
Between the two of us, you're the one
بيننا الاثنين، أنت الوحيد
who took the loss,
من تحمل الخسارة
while I'm the one who got the better end.
بينما أنا من حصل على النهاية الأفضل.
(Got the better end...)
(حصلت على النهاية الأفضل...)
(She still sees our marriage as a deal.)
(ما زالت ترى زواجنا بمثابة صفقة.)
Zhou Tingyan,
تشو تينغيان,
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I really like it.
أنا حقا أحب ذلك.
♪The heart is as fragile as glass♪
♪القلب هش كالزجاج♪
♪Longing always comes during the night♪
♪الشوق يأتي دائمًا أثناء الليل♪
♪Tears at the corner of my eyes, a trembling voice♪
♪الدموع في زاوية عيني، صوت مرتجف♪
♪You walk right into my dreams again♪
♪أنت تمشي مباشرة إلى أحلامي مرة أخرى♪
♪Your love is a rare luxury♪
♪حبك هو ترف نادر♪
I'm now Mrs. Zhou.
أنا الآن السيدة تشو.
♪All I can do is let it settle down♪
♪كل ما يمكنني فعله هو ترك الأمر يستقر♪
♪Back to zero♪
♪العودة إلى الصفر♪
(The proposal's already done.)
(تم تقديم الاقتراح بالفعل.)
(So his next move would be...)
(لذا فإن خطوته التالية ستكون...)
Uh…
أوه…
The bathroom's...
الحمام...
Where is it?
أين هي؟
I'll take you there.
سوف آخذك إلى هناك.
Hey.
يا.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I can find it myself.
أستطيع أن أجده بنفسي.
Have Aunt Fang lead you.
اطلب من العمة فانغ أن تقودك.
♪Tears at the corner of my eyes, a trembling voice♪
♪الدموع في زاوية عيني، صوت مرتجف♪
♪You walk right into my dreams again♪
♪أنت تمشي مباشرة إلى أحلامي مرة أخرى♪
♪Your love is a rare luxury♪
♪حبك هو ترف نادر♪
♪So hard for me to reach♪
♪من الصعب جدًا بالنسبة لي الوصول إليه♪
How is she?
كيف حالها؟
Don't worry, sir.
لا تقلق يا سيدي.
Aside from what's visible,
بصرف النظر عما هو مرئي،
she has no other injuries.
ليس لديها أي إصابات أخرى.
I avoided the wounds when I helped her bathe.
لقد تجنبت الجروح عندما ساعدتها على الاستحمام.
Mm.
مم.
Turn off the light.
أطفئ الضوء.
Feeling sleepy?
هل تشعر بالنعاس؟
Mm.
مم.
Jian Cheng.
جيان تشنغ.
Things like this...
أشياء مثل هذا...
can't be rushed.
لا يمكن التسرع.
You're not eager?
أنت لست متشوقًا؟
Then why insist on coming today?
إذن لماذا الإصرار على المجيء اليوم؟
Well,
حسنًا،
didn't you say it'd take five minutes?
ألم تقل أن الأمر سيستغرق خمس دقائق؟
It'll be over fast.
سوف ينتهي الأمر سريعا.
Five minutes?
خمس دقائق؟
Mm.
مم.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Weren't those your own words?
ألم تكن تلك كلماتك الخاصة؟
Five minutes, right?
خمس دقائق، أليس كذلك؟
The five minutes I meant
الخمس دقائق التي قصدتها
was to give you the ring
كان من المفترض أن أعطيك الخاتم
and propose to you.
وأقترح عليك.
Then...
ثم...
when did you buy this ring?
متى اشتريت هذا الخاتم؟
A long time ago.
منذ زمن طويل.
Zhou Tingyan.
تشو تينغيان.
Every new chapter
كل فصل جديد
needs a new beginning.
يحتاج إلى بداية جديدة.
I can do that.
انا قادر على فعل ذلك.
You can start counting.
يمكنك البدء في العد.
See how many five minutes it really is.
انظر كم خمس دقائق هي في الحقيقة.
♪Late at night, I count the fleeting seconds♪
♪في وقت متأخر من الليل، أحسب الثواني العابرة♪
♪Among the crowd, I search for your gaze♪
♪بين الحشد، أبحث عن نظراتك♪
♪How deep is the secret in my heart?♪
♪ما مدى عمق السر في قلبي؟♪
♪Drawing closer under the label of friends♪
♪الاقتراب من بعضنا البعض تحت مسمى الأصدقاء♪
♪I'm afraid to disturb your peace♪
♪أخشى أن أزعج سلامك♪
♪So I protect, never daring to ask for more♪
♪لذا فأنا أحمي، ولا أجرؤ أبدًا على طلب المزيد♪
♪My eyes follow with a devotion♪
♪عيناي تتبع ذلك بإخلاص♪
♪It's the only thing I take to heart♪
♪إنه الشيء الوحيد الذي آخذه على محمل الجد♪
♪The heart is as fragile as glass♪
♪القلب هش كالزجاج♪
♪Longing always comes during the night♪
♪الشوق يأتي دائمًا أثناء الليل♪
♪Tears at the corner of my eyes, a trembling voice♪
♪الدموع في زاوية عيني، صوت مرتجف♪
♪You walk right into my dreams again♪
♪أنت تمشي مباشرة إلى أحلامي مرة أخرى♪
♪Your love is a rare luxury♪
♪حبك هو ترف نادر♪
♪So hard for me to reach♪
♪من الصعب جدًا بالنسبة لي الوصول إليه♪
♪All I can do is let it settle down♪
♪كل ما يمكنني فعله هو ترك الأمر يستقر♪
♪Back to zero♪
♪العودة إلى الصفر♪